Hello dears.  Welcome to the vlog.  I
just got out of the pool.  Today I had
both a bike and a swimming pool.  I trained,
I practiced.  There were more exercises today
,
so let me tell you, it was nice, nice.
I'm a little hungry.  I need to eat something.
Recently I found such a nice
protein sandwich at Żabka.  I'll show you soon.
We'll come over.  They'll bake it some more.  This
is so good and so filling and I'm
craving it right now.  We're
flying too.
This is what the sandwich looks like.  We have
bread, chicken, dried fruit, dried
tomatoes, and lettuce.  I didn't have time
to show you the packaging because these
girls started talking to me.  Later I gave the lady a
sandwich to heat up and I forgot, but I'll
put a picture of that
sandwich somewhere and I'll show you what other ones there
are.  Well, there is a bit of protein as well as
fat, but this sandwich is really very
good.  Give it a try and
be sure to heat it up, because oh my
goodness, it's delicious and, above all,
very filling.  I ate a sandwich, but
I also went to the parcel locker because
my parcel arrived and now I don't know if they
are gels.  Gels or not.  We'll see.
We'll see soon.   I think
so.  These are T-shirts.   I'm so
happy.  y, two
cycling jerseys, because I actually have two,
one of which I love, and the other one is
still a bit tight on me, so I
had to get myself two such jerseys
, because, you know, you sweat
when I have day after day, for example,
training, so I miss these jerseys.
Mommy comes up to me, she let me
pet her today.
Yes, you need to visit them more often
.
But you see, the kittens aren't coming over
yet.
Lodz, are you waiting for us?  We're going to the
cottage soon.  [laughter]
But look how sweet it is when they
play.   I
got you.
Come here.  Oh, you wait.  Oh you, wait.
But there will be an attack now.  Look, mom,
look what the attack will be like.
Oh, [laughter] he
'll walk backwards.
Oh,
the tails are moving.
Oh, oh,
and this is the girl at the top.  And where
is the third one?
And he hid somewhere.
Oh, to mommy.  Oh Jesus, how she licks him.
How sweet.  This one looks very much like mom
, doesn't it?
These spots are so beautiful.  [laughter]
Oh, here he comes.  Jesus, this girl is beautiful
.
She didn't eat before, now she came.   They've
already eaten their fill.
[laughter]
This one is such a troublemaker, isn't it?  Oh,
oh,
look, [laughter] that's not
enough for him.  Oh you, oh you, oh you.
[laughter]
What cuties, huh?  Hello dears.  Welcome
to another day.  Mommy and I will be making
tomatoes today.
Well, they were so abundant that I
made myself a nice
sandwich today.  I baked some bread in the
oven.  On top of that I put
avocado, mozzarella cheese, tomato and
a little bit of magic.
Oh my,
you're the pick.  Selective and appetizing.  We still
have tomatoes here,
so we'll make them with mom,
we'll just do them gradually, because it's a
shame.  We just won't eat it and
will make tomato soup.
Of course it is.  Did you see what
happened to me again?
Look, my dears, I cured myself and my
watch burned me again.
Well, well, that's not
good [laughter] that's
not good.   Let's get started
.   Yes Sir
.  We are already showing.  Do I have and
will we cut them in half?
I think not.
No, I think the thermomix will do the trick, right?   He'll be fine
.  These, these are already
rinsed.  These need to be rinsed.
And you had them weighed, because I took a couple
.
No,
no.  Aha, so these need to be rinsed.
Okay, it doesn't have to be a
strictly
weighted proportion.  All right.
Mhm.  We pour it in.
Oh, oh,
oh. They are running away,
running away, running away, running away.
Oh,
he carried the Shar through the desert.
And the Thermomix will handle it.
[snort]
For how long?
Oh, full blast.  First,
please tell me how it was mixed.
Show me, show me what you were cutting for.  Elegantly.
Jesus, all the lyrics remind me of
some song.
Wait, we'll pour it in.
Throw these tomatoes in there right away.
Yes.
Rinsed.
Hello, poterek.  How many moms do you care?
All.  All.
All.   Oh
please.
And they will be just right.
And still at full volume.  Yes,
yes, yes, full blast.
No, that's a good idea.  It's your
pity.   Well
, we won't accept it.
My mom and I were supposed to
make these tomatoes yesterday, but there was a storm and there was a
power cut.  Although, let me put it this way, it
thundered, thundered, rained,
rained and suddenly there was no electricity.  I already woke up
, it was electricity.  I don't know what time they
turned it on.
And probably after midnight.
And I was already asleep.  I was so tired after
training that I said I'm going to sleep, because sleep
is also very good for
regeneration.
Now the dears will be cooking.  How much,
mom?
Well, to evaporate some water.   We'll
add salt and a little sugar to show
how thick it is.
For what?  Color,
so that the tomatoes have color.
How much salt did you put in?   A
spoon.   A
spoonful of salt, a teaspoon of sugar.   I'll
buy two teaspoons
to preserve the color.
Only four came out.
Yes, there
were that many tomatoes.
Well [laughter] but it evaporated.
Oh okay.
Well, that's so
pretty.  Do we still have tomatoes in the
garden?
Yes.  Well, they will still mature.   I do
n't know if anyone drove up.
I'll check
what came in there soon.
Gels, because I'm out of them.  I had those gels for a long time
, because I recently ordered some
lovely gels from the same company, but
unfortunately I didn't like the taste.
My favorite gels are these, I'm
showing you these now.
Well, I was tempted because those were on
sale [laughter]
and it cost me four something.  Well, I
simply didn't like them, but I won't
show which ones, because maybe someone won't like them
.  Yes.  However, here,
here, bars should also come for
cycling.
And I don't know what it is.
Probably
so.  Oh, these are such bars, I'll
need them because I have a Grand Fondo
in Warsaw and a Grand Fondo in Toruń.  During
training, I only take one gel and
one bar, and I don't
use it anymore because the trainer teaches me to
use my own energy resources,
to use it as little as possible.  Unless it's during a
competition, so during a competition, let
's say four gels and a bar, but that's
also after a few kilometers.  Well,
if you're curious, let me know and I'll
explain it a little more.
My, what a talker he is.  [laughter]
I'd like to show you the T-
shirts that arrived, because I did
n't open them yesterday, so I'll
try them on with you today.  Eh, wait
a minute.   We're
currently on a break from cleaning.
Here I will be very visible on my bike.
All right.
And black, because I wanted a black one too
.  I'll try it on soon and show you.
Well, I'm curious.   I
miss these shirts.   I do
n't know.  I actually have one that
will be cool
and I invite you.   This is what it
looks like.
Oh cool.  Great.
And it has reflectors on the back.   Yeah.
Oh, and he has these.
Oh, you see, elegansio.   It
still has pockets.
What a neat girl.
E,
it will be,
it will be.  But I'll tell you, it looks great with those
extra shorts.   I
have one more.  T-shirts are generally
expensive, and this one was really nice on
sale.  99.99
cost 4F
and loose.  This one will be for colder days
because it is black.  I think maybe we'll
see today.
And I'll show you one more that I have for
this heat.  Although I
try not to drive in this heat, but you know what I
mean.  If there is sun, then that one will be
there.
Mhm.
And this one is like this.
Oh, you're welcome.  But how pretty.
Mom, don't use your phone like that,
[laughter] because the image will be unstable.  The one
that will be visible.
I'll tell you, yes.  And with this
color scheme it looks nice.  Oh,
you'll be showing off on the road.
[laughter]
Well, listen to how viewers catch me on
the way to take photos, even though sometimes
I'm really fast and I don't
stop because I feel bad about it, because I have to
put in a lot of effort to get up to
speed, but when they catch me somewhere
, they'll have me in a
different outfit now,
not in one all the time.  [laughter] It's not that
this one could be,
but that sometimes I need it
overnight and it won't dry, or I forget
to wash it right away, or there are no dark ones and
only one.   There is
no need to dry it, because here it dries once or twice
.   It's just that you have to, you know,
wait for the
others.  Well, you won't
wash just one.
Yes, that's right.  Oh well, I was just
asking for it.  I have another
orange one, but
I ordered that one earlier.  I'll show you a moment,
but I still have to lose weight before that.  This one
will fit my bike.
Oh, cool.
It's 4F.
Oh,
cool.
Cool, right?
Well,
well, I'm not buying anymore.  Unless someone
wants to send it to me, then [laughter] I'll ask for it.   There
's never too much of it, so
you know, especially when you
start riding.
Yes.
Well, this one is beautiful too.  Well, I'm
telling you, it will suit me.  I could also
use some orange shoes,
but it will be gradual and I will
also buy orange or black or white
to match the colors, you have no
idea what I mean.  Even though I have a
bit of that celadon color element
on my helmet, this one will
suit me.  But the shoes don't fit me anymore,
so no.
And those shoes matched that
purple shirt.
You see?  I'm dressing up here.  This is what I
like.
Do my duty to me.
We'll see.
What do we have here?  What do we have here?   I do
n't know if I need to wear glasses
that much?   Yeah.
E,
I'll help.  [laughter]
I'll clean the cabin.
Operating Instructions  All right.
Okay, this is probably for the cabin.
Mhm.
I thought I had to
put on that different tip, but
okay, since it's rubber, it won't
scratch.
[snort] read.
[laughter]
Next instruction.  You see, this is how
fast you read.
[laughter]
[snort] I learned math so quickly
.
We help, mommy.
Yes, you help.
This is where it comes in.
Oh,
he, womb is, is.
Womb.  [snort]
And what next?  You probably need to press something on
that brush.
Yes, but it needs to warm up first.
Let it warm up.
Wait, we have to read it first.
Lady looks bored.  Don't worry, Lady.
I also
need to get out of here, because it's steam, so she does
n't get scared here, she doesn't
get burned anywhere.
Okay, come on Dejus, let's go.  Stay put
, okay, wait there.
Okay, so here we have the bigger pair and
this one is smaller.
Yes.  Oh Jesus, this is the first time I've ever experienced this. Oh damn, does
it even touch?
Yes.
Okay.  Do I poop first?
[snort]
Be careful
not to look at your hand.   I
thought he was going to be pissed off like that at first.
No, no, no, no.  It goes like this.
[snort]
I read that you have to use a special
agent that you first put on the
shower cabin and only then
take the steamer.  Because this steam cleaner is
better at removing dirt such as
grease
or other types of dirt.  No,
not too strong.
You need to use some preparation and then
remove it,
because steam alone won't handle it.   That's what
I read.   So,
no, no
, but it helped a little here and there, but it didn't
help.
Because it doesn't settle here.  Yes.  Well,
they show it off brilliantly here.
Oh wow,
cool.
Okay, this is where he surprised me.
Wow.
Well, you see.  Oh, you see, the dirt
from what Mom and I washed off is stuck here
.
Well, it gets into these nooks and crannies.  Well, it
looks great, this will get you there.
Look how much of it there is here.   Well,
I see it now.  Well, because it's from all
corners, and it can't be done manually.
Unfortunately.   Here you go
.  Now the walls from above.
The walls are crumbling,
the windows are shattering.
It goes.   I don't think it's going
.
Well, this is
going weird.   It
goes
, it goes, it goes, it
goes, it goes.   It's
a bit uncomfortable here,
but it will improve with a cloth.
Well, it cleans nicely.
They scare us.
So what?
Would you like such a person to clean?
These are years of practice, my dears,
experience.
NO.
And in general, my dears, this is what befits us.   We
can't take it out.  Mom even
cut her hand.  Show mom what
you're going to spray.
And now I will have a clean cabin.
Well, that's all you need, my dears, because it stinks terribly
.
Well, he rocks hard, though
But it will dissolve.
All right.
And now so that it
catches evenly.
Oh,
he must dissolve this stone.   Oh,
and we just did this at the cabin.
And where is the rest to clean up?
Well, it will go down a bit.
Ouch, she should be wearing gloves,
but I'm holding it with my
fingernails.
Listen, dears, if you want to
give us some advice, and you have this equipment,
some advice, or, I don't know, write whether we're
doing something wrong or something too well,
[laughter]
then write.  We won't always
learn something because it's the first time we have this
equipment.
What kind of person would you be? I'm taking it
now I have to go in and warm up someone
.   Do
you press while it's warming up or
not?
Well, the water flowed.
Okay.  Are you pressing
now?  Yes.
I only pressed it once.  I had to bandage my mother
because she had
cut herself.
But I don't know if I should shorten
it.
I think so, because it will be inconvenient for you
to give you the shorter one?  A no, because without
A it is nothing.  The tiles are there.
Well, now that's nice.
How did mom put this
special remedy.
Well, now it's gone.
Wow, she's pretty
now.  Nicely washed.
Now still here.
Mom and I continue cleaning.
Let me put it this way, it takes a while, it can't be
done quickly
because the worst part is the
cleaning cabin.  The hardest.
No, fugues.
Grouts,
a bit of grout,
yes, but all these nooks and crannies, the cabin
is made of glass, so it also comes off to be
descaled and then washed.  Well, we did a bit of work
, but together we worked together.
Well, let me tell you, we both had something to do.
Yes, yes, but it relaxes me a lot.
In other words, cleaning
awaits you.
I see.  Well, that's no problem.  Listen, no
problem.  So
no, but together it's more pleasant and more
fun, of course.  Sometimes mom goes to
rest, sometimes I go to rest.
Dear friends, if you liked this casual vlog
, please like,
comment
and subscribe to stay up to
date with all the videos [laughter].
Remember this.  Well, kisses,
take care.  bye